So, Rato, what have we learned in this lesson?
>> Well, I learned that I do not want to write
databases and content providers. What did you learn in this lesson?
>> Well, J unit tests are awesome, and building
the back end framework of our apps is the
most glorious of work. It's an absolutely vital part
of creating a robust app with a great user experience.
>> And I also learned that Dan cannot do an English accent.
>> [SOUND]. Fortunately, you can get ready to welcome back Katherine
for lesson 5, where we'll shatter our activity into fragments, use
our content providers to populate more complex UIs, and build layouts
that work as well on tablets as they do on phones.
>> Which seems like a convenient segway
into the history and evolution of Android hardware,